&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是一个永远令人沮丧的地方
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's a place where it is perpetually frustrating
我们已经超载了运算符。
that we have overloaded operators.
我们倾向于认为花括号一定是作用域。
We tend to think that curly braces must be scopes.
它们是块，它们是函数体，它们必须是作用域。
They're blocks, they're function bodies, they must be scopes.
当我在第三行定义一个箭头函数时会发生什么？
What's gonna happen when I define an arrow function on line three?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：该箭头所来自的父词法范围是什么
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What is the parent lexical scope from which that arrow
函数将上一级来解决？
function will go up one level to resolve the?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：全球？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Global?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它是全球性的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is the global.
它不是车间对象，因为，你猜怎么着？
It is not the workshop object because, guess what?
仅仅因为该对象周围有花括号并不能使其成为范围。
Just cuz there's curly braces around that object doesn't make it a scope.
对象不是作用域。
Objects are not scopes.
所以这是人们经常犯的错误，有几百个
So this is a very common mistake that people have, and there's hundreds of
关于Stack溢出的问题已经到了这种程度，人们都在说，
questions on Stack Overflow to this extent, where people are saying,
为什么箭头功能不能将我的工作坊作为我的内容？
why is the arrow function not getting my workshop as my content?
因为车间对象不是作用域。
Well, because workshop object's not a scope.
你必须认为箭头函数没有这个和
You have to think about an arrow function as not having of this and
从词汇上解决。
resolving it lexically.
那么父作用域是什么？
So what is the parent scope?
这个程序只有两个作用域。
There's only two scopes in this program.
Ask函数的作用域(箭头)和全局作用域。
The scope of the ask function, which is an arrow, and the global scope.
在两者之间没有干预范围。
There's no intervening scope in between.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不幸的是，我们已经超载了
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is unfortunate that we've overloaded the curly brace that
迷惑我们认为它是一个范围，但它不是。
confuses us into thinking it's a scope, but it isn't.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以如果你把所有这些细微差别都带到箭头上
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So if you take all of this nuance around arrow
函数和这些关键字。
functions and these keywords.
如果你考虑到我之前的评论，
If you take it into account with my former comments on,
我认为箭头函数，缺点是箭头函数是匿名的
I think arrow functions, the downside is that arrow functions are anonymous and
所以它们有时更难被窃听，它们不能很好地解释自己。
so they're a bit harder to bug at times, they don't explain themselves well.
如果你考虑整个上下文，
If you take the entire context,
我的看法是，只有在你应该使用箭头功能的时候
my perception is that the only time you should ever use an arrow function
就是什么时候你才能从这种行为中受益。
is when you're gonna benefit from lexical this behavior.
因为除了lexical之外，这种行为是一种黑客行为
Because the alternative to lexical this behavior is a hack
就像var self等于这种情况。
like the var self equals this case.
当然，你们中的一些人已经看到了代码，其中var self等于这个
Surely, some of you have seen code where you did var self equals this and
然后引用单元格。
then you reference the cell.
或者它被称为var that或者var强调这个，或者其他什么。
Or maybe it was called var that or var underscore this, or whatever.
我只想说，var self等于这是最糟糕的名字
Let me just say, var self equals this is the worst possible name
任何人都能想出。
anybody ever could have come up with.
因为这个关键字永远，在任何情况下，
Because this keyword never, ever, ever, under any circumstances,
指向函数本身，则指向上下文。
points at the function itself, it points at a context.
所以如果你绝对必须让var self等于这个黑客，
So if you absolutely must do the var self equal this hack,
请做var context等于这个。
please do var context equals this.
因为这就是这个关键字，是一个上下文，好吗？
Cuz that's what this keyword is, is a context, okay?
但此箭头函数对此行为进行词法分析
But this arrow function lexical this behavior
是一种比var self等于这更好的方式。
is a much better way of doing it than a var self equals this.
我会说比做这个功能更好。绑定。
And I would argue even better than doing the function.bind.
这是一种更好的方式，因为它实际上符合
It is a much better way because it actually matches the mental model of
我们想要的。
what we want.
我们希望this关键字在这里表现得像词汇一样。
We want the this keyword to behave lexically here.
我们不想让箭头函数对它有一些神奇的这种行为。
We don't want for the arrow function to have some magical this behavior to it.
我们希望它只采用某个父作用域的this关键字。
We want it to just adopt the this keyword of some parent scope.
这就是它所做的，所以它是正确的工具设计来修复正确的
And that's what it does, so it is the right tool designed to fix the right
问题，如果你倾向于正确思考它的话。
problem, if you're inclined to think correctly about it.
所以，尽管我已经说过，一般情况下，不要使用箭头函数，如果你在一个案例中，比如
So whereas I've said, generally, don't use arrow functions, if you're in a case, like
几张幻灯片前的setTimeout，在那里你有理由需要词法this，
a couple slides ago with the setTimeout, where you legitimately need lexical this,
请使用箭头功能，因为这是适合这项工作的工具。
please use the arrow function, cuz that's the right tool for the job.
事实上，我甚至写了一个ESLint规则，
As a matter of fact, I went so far as to write an ESLint rule,
这需要您的箭头函数来进行引用，
that requires your arrow functions to make this references,
它不允许任何没有使用词法this的箭头函数。
it disallows any arrow function that is not using lexical this.
这是极具争议性的
That's extremely controversial,
我知道，不太可能有很多人会使用ESLint规则。
I know, unlikely that very many people are ever gonna use that ESLint rule.
但如果你像我一样认为箭头函数有这个目的
But if you, like me, think that arrow functions have that purpose and
这就是他们应该用来做的
that's what they ought to be used for,
这是一个插件，它将为您提供控制该行为的规则。
that's a plug-in that will give you a rule to control that behavior.
问题。
Questions.
是啊。
Yes.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：只是确认一下。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Just to confirm.
回到一张幻灯片，所以当我们，当我们解析这个，
Going back one slide, so when we’re, when we would be parsing this,
车间正在进入红色的桶，它正在获得全球范围。
workshop is going into the red bucket, it’s getting the global scope.
然而，教师财产的范围将是-
The teacher property, though, would be scoped to-
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：属性不是作用域，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Properties aren't scoped,
属性不是词汇标识符。
properties aren't lexical identifiers.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的，明白了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay, got you.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它是对象值的成员。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's a member on an object value.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它没有参与
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's not participating
在词汇范围内。
in lexical scope at all.
我唯一的例外就是不要使用箭头函数，因为它们是匿名的，
My one and only exception to the don't use arrow functions because they're anonymous,
当您可以从词法this中受益时，请使用箭头函数。
is use arrow functions when you can benefit from the lexical this.
不过，我会说，
I will however say,
如果你要使用箭头函数来获得你的词法this，你需要对抗
that if you gonna use an arrow function to get your lexical this, you need to combat
这三个缺点，我们在匿名函数中讨论过。
those three downsides that we talked about with anonymous function.
你需要克服匿名函数不具备的缺点
You need to combat the downside that, anonymous functions don't
有一个自我引用，以防你需要做递归或解除绑定。
have a self reference, in case you need to do recursion or unbinding.
你需要与他们没有名字的事实作斗争。
You need to combat the fact that they don't have a name.
以某种方式使用它，这样它就会得到一个名称推断，就像，
Use it in some way so that it's gonna get a name inference, like,
将其分配给变量或属性。
assign it to a variable or a property.
因为否则它会以匿名的形式出现。
Because it's gonna show up as anonymous otherwise.
而且你需要有一些方法让读者明白和明白这一点。
And you need to have some way of making it clear and obvious to the reader.
这个函数的目的是什么？
What is the purpose of this function?
不要让他们读取函数体来理解这一点。
Don't make them read the function body to figure that out.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在我们已经讨论了this关键字。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So now we've talked about the this keyword.
我们已经看到了它所有不同的角度，让我激动的是
We've seen all of its different angles, and what I'm thrilled about actually is
箭头函数不是this关键字的不同规则。
that the arrow function is not a different rule for the this keyword.
当他们添加箭头函数时，我很害怕，我们必须对其进行修改
I was afraid when they were adding arrow functions that we were gonna have to amend
这些规则，并且有第五条规则在我们的脑海中漂浮，但它不是一条规则
these rules, and have a fifth rule to keep floating in our head, but it's not a rule
因为this关键字甚至不适用于箭头函数。
at all because the this keyword doesn't even apply instead of arrow functions.
要理解this关键字，唯一需要做的事情就是查找
The only thing you ever need to do to understand the this keyword is look for
定义this关键字的函数的调用位置，以及
the call site of a function that defines the this keyword, and
问那四条规则。
ask those four rules.